<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Entertainment - Bing News</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/news/search?q=&amp;p1=%5bNewsVertical+Category%3d%22rt_Entertainment%22%5d&amp;FORM=NWBTCB&amp;format=RSS</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <copyright>Copyright \xc2\xa9 2014 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <pubDate>7/30/2014 5:44:30 PM</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING NEWS: Drew Barrymore's half-sister 'found dead in her car' in California</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2fnews%2farticle-2710608%2fBREAKING-NEWS-Drew-Barrymores-half-sister-dead-car-California.html&amp;c=fKbWnSRUima-XIfWWcRhE-FG5ypWGVa8sKw6qAgHB9M&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Drew Barrymore's half-sister Jessica found dead in California","summary":["Jessica Barrymore, 47, was found dead in her car in National City, just north of San Diego, on Tuesday.","Jessica Barrymore, 47, was found dead in her car yesterday from a suspected suicide  Marta Lopez made the discovery when she tried to leave for work but was blocked in her driveway by Ms Barrymore's car, 10News reported.","She unsuccessfully tried to wake Ms Barrymore, who was to turn 48 tomorrow, before calling the police."],"source":"dailymail.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Bloom threw a punch at Justin Bieber at Spanish hotspot, report says</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.foxnews.com%2fentertainment%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2forlando-bloom-threw-punch-at-justin-bieber-at-spanish-hotspot-report-says%2f&amp;c=rEmIuvNVHZQil8h3BscTbsDCGKt6OHk7IOsrToPv48s&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Orlando Bloom threw a punch at Justin Bieber at Spanish hotspot, report says","summary":["After getting in each other\u00e2\u0080\u0099s faces\u00e2\u0080\u0094Bloom threw a punch at the pop star\u00e2\u0080\u0094the crowd cheered.","The bad blood between the two began in 2012 when Bieber was seen getting flirty with Kerr, which reportedly led to tension between the model and her then-husband, Bloom.","Then newly single Bloom was seen spending time with Bieber\u00e2\u0080\u0099s ex-girlfriend, Selena Gomez, in April."],"source":"foxnews.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ariana Grande Opens Up About Her Confidence Problem</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.people.com%2farticle%2fariana-grande-insecurities-confidence&amp;c=PkHEk-Ls9yLzME-b04BXhn9EJIFfkfx_TKr8uxFEMys&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Ariana Grande Opens Up About Her Confidence Problem","summary":[" She's the vocal powerhouse behind what is shaping up to be the song of the summer, but even Ariana Grande hasn't always felt confident.","Grande says she found strength in her grandfather, who died last week.","However, she also names the estrangement with her father as the toughest thing she's had to deal with to date."],"source":"people.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the road again: Echo and the Bunnymen hop the pond</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.usatoday.com%2fstory%2flife%2fmusic%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fecho-and-the-bunnymen-american-tour-on-the-road-again%2f13348361%2f&amp;c=qO6ZIsZI6JzvxpzWwfXLMy7UHH9gkcE4p4qP3kY3uNc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Echo and the Bunnymen hop the pond","summary":["It is hard sometimes to go, no, we're not playing this.","When they got it started again, they played one song continuously for 20 minutes because they couldn't figure out how to turn the thing off.","They just stand there, while this fella struggles with this box?"],"source":"usatoday.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: Josie Cunningham defends selling birth tickets: "It isn't sexual" - as Mirror follows controversial model for day</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.mirror.co.uk%2f3am%2fcelebrity-news%2flive-josie-cunningham-defends-selling-3934657&amp;c=8nAgTTqI5ioMf6F0W_mw7xQ4ij6Nu2DnZVQuJa21tGI&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"LIVE: Josie Cunningham defends selling birth tickets: \"It isn't sexual\" - as Mirror follows controversial model for day","source":"mirror.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street smarts: Dapper Daniel Radcliffe looks the business as he leaves Jimmy Kimmel Live! surrounded by security</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2ftvshowbiz%2farticle-2710534%2fDaniel-Radcliffe-looks-smart-leaves-Jimmy-Kimmel-Live-surrounded-security.html&amp;c=usKlAG3eDq9zHKVsbcEr-6Zjlc5M93NJbrXw2QrqagA&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>He recently tricked fans at the Comic-Con convention by going incognito in a Spider-Man costume. But there was no mistaking Daniel Radcliffe as he hit the streets of Hollywood following an appearance on Jimmy Kimmel Live! on Tuesday. Looking dapper in a ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 obscene celebrity rants in support of Israel’s assault on Gaza</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.salon.com%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2f6_obscene_celebrity_rants_in_support_of_israels_assault_on_gaza_partner%2f&amp;c=Xg0zRmDWotMZLEAWzsmKHMe-lFO61Nqk6DK8QNK7_zo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Israeli assault on Gaza has sparked intense, and often vitriolic, debate across the U.S., and the entertainment business is no exception. A number of Hollywood celebrities have come out in protest of the bombardment of the people of Gaza by Israeli ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Idle performs theme song for The Infinite Monkey Cage</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.co.uk%2fprogrammes%2fp021x88c&amp;c=MljksghhfpKsFxiIWRaCmaxsHLjaYndh3DwdGh0U8Nw&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Brian Cox and Robin Ince join Eric Idle as he sings his new song about the programme. (Song written, produced and performed by Eric Idle and Jeff Lynne. Video produced by Trunkman Productions. Puppets made by Beth Crane.)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Jonas And Demi Lovato Recorded The ‘Perfect’ Song For His Record</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.mtv.com%2fnews%2f1883167%2fnick-jonas-demi-lovato-duet%2f&amp;c=u1ZYXdZiN7QudR3aAtfQeUcOhT5_CEK9CItQxg3g0Do&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Nick Jonas and Demi Lovato have been teasing a potential duet for months now. Hell, just a few weeks ago, Lovato posted a pic of two thumbs up and said she was working on a “KILLER” collabo. Now the former Jonas Brothers member (and creative and ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star War 7: Harrison Ford pictured walking solo without crutch after breaking leg on Millennium Falcon</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.mirror.co.uk%2ftv%2ftv-news%2fstar-war-7-harrison-ford-3935464&amp;c=7ZBu7xDpy-MB9LtZ3tPp5wvaWPWJt6zz35AfhQzXJ3g&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Han Solo star, Harrison Ford, was snapped walking without a crutch after previously being pictured using an iWalk aid at an airport in Santa Monica, California. Star Wars actor Harrison looked a lot more comfortable, as he continues his recovery from a ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tu Mere Agal Bagal Hai actors give part of income for charity</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ftimesofindia.indiatimes.com%2fentertainment%2fhindi%2ftv%2fnews%2fTu-Mere-Agal-Bagal-Hai-actors-give-part-of-income-for-charity%2farticleshow%2f39298147.cms&amp;c=us2fRrVh0RClN_KcATrxQ9Utqa9vDyVj2gbgsbAo_rQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Tu Mere AgalBagalHai is a light-hearted stand-up fiction comedy show that exhibits the comical happenings in the daily lives of all the members residing in Bungalow No. 6. The actors spread cheer and happiness amongst their viewers through their unique ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emraan Hashmi doesn't find himself ideal for Sooraj Barjatya's films</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ftimesofindia.indiatimes.com%2fentertainment%2fhindi%2fbollywood%2fnews%2fEmraan-Hashmi-doesnt-find-himself-ideal-for-Sooraj-Barjatyas-films%2farticleshow%2f39299510.cms&amp;c=7uOl0LS_9ZOrUE26WHSgjGR219EdEEiRRORTD-2j00s&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Emraan Hashmi has become identified with various genres of thrillers and, therefore, the actor doesn't see himself fitting into the social or family drama mould. In his over-a-decade-long career, the actor has worked with filmmakers like Ekta Kapoor ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katy Perry and Diplo Party Together in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.people.com%2farticle%2fkaty-perry-diplo-partying-las-vegas-xs-andreas-at-encore&amp;c=MdoJ3NZEjMAHZRWTx_P8mgTkiUfxCRh6aR_ayvBWuto&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Katy Perry truly goes all out for birthdays. The "Dark Horse" singer and an entourage of close friends partied in Vegas Monday night at XS nightclub to celebrate a pal's birthday. With rumored love interest Diplo spinning at the deejay booth, Perry, 29 ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 03:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Upon a Time stars talk season 3, Frozen and romance</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.digitalspy.co.uk%2fustv%2fs181%2fonce-upon-a-time%2finterviews%2fa586720%2fonce-upon-a-time-stars-talk-season-3-frozen-and-romance.html&amp;c=w8TDDs3p4ZbJ8XEnCzHmv09Z6dMrrCi4TOCZzSRKukQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Frozen is coming to Once Upon a Time... but how do the show's stars feel about it? Speaking to Digital Spy at Comic-Con International in San Diego, the cast of ABC's hit fantasy series reveal how Frozen and Once Upon a Time will collide this fall.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you have what it takes to sing like Mabrrr?</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.sowetanlive.co.za%2fentertainment%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fdo-you-have-what-it-takes-to-sing-like-mabrrr&amp;c=9oNx_XK276EDEahNq2patV2rORgU79RZdzi-_Gsrldo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Could there be another Fassie out there to blow the music industry away and shine like the original Brenda? Johannesburg Arts Alive International Festival announced the search for this one of a kind pop star yesterday. Auditions are set to be held on ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones star Maisie Williams hits out at "snobby" book fans</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.digitalspy.co.uk%2fustv%2fs151%2fgame-of-thrones%2fnews%2fa587370%2fgame-of-thrones-star-maisie-williams-hits-out-at-snobby-book-fans.html&amp;c=ELl5DOlMAzcJXc4Fh8tjFQmKbYSPg1IhO7SZuXflkHg&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Williams told TVLine that she dislikes "mean" book readers who spoil the series for fans who have only seen the HBO TV series. "I'm so sick of going on the internet and seeing all the book readers being snobby, spoiling it for other people - then saying ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-List Insider: Prince Harry Photobomb, Shakira Pregnant with Second Child</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.ibtimes.co.uk%2ftv%2flist-insider-prince-harry-photobomb-shakira-pregnant-second-child-11898&amp;c=AHKDrVgZFF3zK4c0YiOo3nhy31ZIuK4rQf1sBSmUIew&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>In this week's A-List Insider: First it was the Queen and now it looks like Prince Harry has got in on the photo bombing action too. Here is the moment the cheeky royal decided that he would have some fun at the commonwealth games by sticking his head in ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Bloom Reportedly Tried to Punch Justin Bieber</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fabcnews.go.com%2fEntertainment%2forlando-bloom-reportedly-punch-justin-bieber%2fstory%3fid%3d24768982&amp;c=Yv3Dnq1xk4OaQ5cZNmxSzijreDdachvNBkrHg3U9_wU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Actor Orlando Bloom reportedly tried to punch Justin Bieber at an Ibiza, Spain, night spot early Wednesday, with part of the apparent confrontation captured on video by fellow partiers. Bieber can be heard shouting what sounds on the video like “What’s ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See Melanie Griffith Cover Up 'Antonio' Tattoo With Her Own Name</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fabcnews.go.com%2fEntertainment%2fmelanie-griffith-cover-antonio-tattoo%2fstory%3fid%3d24763716&amp;c=oa1-K608twL27VB6yR35C-x8AQadfTCod6zXZzpnrJ0&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>You have to give her style points. After announcing her split from Antonio Banderas early in June, Melanie Griffith, 56, was seen a week later covering up her "Antonio" tattoo with what appeared to be makeup as she walked various red carpets. Now, she has ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Bloom Throws Punch at Justin Bieber</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=531815ec857a4af6a4af73ec6b7dade1&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.tmz.com%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2forlando-bloom-justin-bieber-ibiza-fight-bar-miranda-kerr%2f&amp;c=yfAYwTQnTZCp4xmXpt_AgXXUw9MzfJqF8a5UZK-Qooc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Orlando Bloom threw a punch at Justin Bieber early Wednesday morning in Ibiza ... and Justin fled the restaurant -- this according to 2 eyewitnesses. The eyewitnesses tell TMZ ... Orlando was in Cipriani restaurant which was packed with celebs, including ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>