<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Business - Bing News</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/news/search?q=&amp;nvaug=%5bNewsVertical+Category%3d%22rt_Business%22%5d&amp;FORM=NSBABR&amp;format=RSS</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <copyright>Copyright \xc2\xa9 2014 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <pubDate>7/30/2014 5:44:36 PM</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine debt talks go down to the wire to avert default</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.todayonline.com%2fbusiness%2ftime-almost-argentina-avoid-debt-default&amp;c=3gNuQnSA6zT6GG49D9EH2KU6fH6qH4Yyn7DLfgM3cTk&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Argentine debt talks go down to the wire to avert default","summary":["Argentina's key dollar bond due 2033 rose sharply on Wednesday, and its debt insurance costs fell as investors took some cheer from the meeting.","Argentina's five-year credit default swaps dropped 30 basis points from Tuesday's close to 1,869 basis points, according to Markit.","The nation's one-year credit default swaps dropped 51 basis points from Tuesday's close to 4,708 basis points."],"source":"todayonline.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald’s Ruling Could Open Door for Unions</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.nytimes.com%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fbusiness%2fnlrb-holds-mcdonalds-not-just-franchisees-liable-for-worker-treatment.html&amp;c=3pFePtdJvfyOMJCXBNHn6zW9sYSJ3EManRXdoR8Yysc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Log In - The New York Times","summary":["Create an account \u00bb  Subscribed through iTunes and need an NYTimes.com account?"],"source":"nytimes.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain accelerates away from crisis: official data</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.businesstimes.com.sg%2fbreaking-news%2fworld%2fspain-accelerates-away-crisis-official-data-20140730&amp;c=G-08F32u-YuGlG2hlKjzuoPbRO-Euez02Xhhey3Qw1E&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Spain accelerates away from crisis: official data, World Breaking News &amp;amp; Headlines","summary":["The latest growth figure was slightly better than expected and marked acceleration from growth of 0.4 per cent in the first quarter.","The figures came the day after the government raised its forecasts saying it hoped growth in Spain, with the fourth-biggest economy in the eurozone, would be close to 1.5 per cent this year and possibly 2.0 per cent next year.","The International Monetary Fund, which now sees the strength of Spain's recovery as a welcome surprise, also raised its forecasts last week for the country's growth this year and next."],"source":"businesstimes.com.sg"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy firms to 'double' profit margins, predicts Ofgem</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.co.uk%2fnews%2fbusiness-28563296&amp;c=NOi7ywjKdrDI2f-b4OAF-ULknpTvOvJTI1AidTj_n3w&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"BBC News - Energy firms to 'double' profit margins, predicts Ofgem","summary":["   30 July 2014 Last updated at 13:02    The big six energy firms are set to double their profit margins over the next year, according to estimates by the regulator, Ofgem.","A year ago, Ofgem estimated that suppliers would make an average profit of \u00a353 per dual fuel customer, a margin of 4%.","However Ofgem - which will officially publish the details on Thursday - said it was further evidence that the market was not working as well as it should."],"source":"bbc.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe flat ahead of Fed, US GDP data</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.ft.com%2fcms%2fs%2f0%2fc1472636-1798-11e4-b0d7-00144feabdc0.html&amp;c=hMUeJzmMVpkpxJGIk1O2rje9EvVGxF_vif2OvIFuqDo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Europe flat ahead of Fed, US GDP data","summary":[" Printed from:  http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/c1472636-1798-11e4-b0d7-00144feabdc0.html  Print a single copy of this article for personal use."],"source":"ft.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays Rises Most Since May on Return to Profit</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bloomberg.com%2fnews%2f2014-07-30%2fbarclays-first-half-profit-fell-7-on-investment-bank.html&amp;c=55wS_VjZbhM4OIkUuU6hym2zqMgrfxcDUg1r0-edFcQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Barclays Plc, the U.K.’s second-largest bank by assets, returned to a profit in the second quarter, helped by lower impairments and cost cuts. The shares jumped the most in almost three months. Barclays’s second-quarter net income was 161 million ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AstraZeneca buys Almirall lung drugs for up to $2.1 billion</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.todayonline.com%2fbusiness%2fastrazeneca-buys-almirall-lung-drugs-21-billion&amp;c=3Z5nVDjqq7imKCQ5c_00SkjVVd0_5Hau7A4ZICosGaU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>LONDON - AstraZeneca took a major step to build up its respiratory medicine business on Wednesday by striking a deal worth up to $2.1 billion for the rights to Spanish group Almirall's lung drugs. The British drugmaker, which resisted a $118 billion ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's economy grows at fastest quarterly rate since 2007</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.co.uk%2fnews%2fbusiness-28559302&amp;c=K2bRS2WyfcZ49inG-0harcyFBqZyWUYG4cUtbz_y8MQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Spanish economy grew at its fastest pace over the last three months since the end of 2007, according to Spain's statistics office. But falling prices show the country is facing a deflation threat after it emerged from a two year recession last year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy seen regaining muscle in second quarter</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.reuters.com%2farticle%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fus-usa-economy-idUSKBN0FZ09P20140730&amp;c=qR4xYq2DCdhzDWyl7nSrGyQ1BYZj6hQ0cd5NMxI_cxU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Gross domestic product likely grew at a 3.0 percent annual rate after shrinking at a 2.9 percent pace in the first quarter, according to a Reuters survey of economists. "I don't think the contraction we saw in the first quarter is reflective of what's ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pfizer refuses to rule out tax inversion deals</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.ft.com%2fcms%2fs%2f0%2fb494286e-171e-11e4-b0d7-00144feabdc0.html&amp;c=LyHBtWzfR79vR8t9XSTq8GnmjjbU5pQSANdqeZSqqyI&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Pfizer has called for “fundamental reform” of the US tax system – but said it was still interested in acquisitions that would allow it to put offshore revenues beyond the reach of the US taxman in the absence of change. Ian Read, chief executive ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Popping Housing Bubbles London Can’t Handle</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bloomberg.com%2fnews%2f2014-07-29%2fsingapore-popping-housing-bubbles-london-can-t-handle.html&amp;c=yzWNChR_hGA4EYF5m8KD4e869PSR06aQpqfUZzKKj-Q&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>July 30 (Bloomberg) -- Prompted by concerns over potential property bubbles and affordability for the middle class, the governments of Hong Kong and Singapore have been reining in home prices by imposing measures including mortgage caps, taxes on property ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoE says banker bonuses can be clawed back for up to seven years</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fuk.reuters.com%2farticle%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fuk-boe-banking-bonuses-idUKKBN0FZ0SB20140730&amp;c=gTwH7QntYBG_anpQnP1n2yuWPrhcQcK4D9SRkXI9VCg&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The measures are the latest response to multi-billion pound taxpayer bailouts of lenders such as Royal Bank of Scotland and Lloyds in the financial crisis of 2008 and 2009, with few individual bankers subsequently punished for reckless behaviour.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2014 Subaru BRZ Earns An IIHS 2014 Top Safety Pick</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ffinance.yahoo.com%2fnews%2f2014-subaru-brz-earns-iihs-120000064.html&amp;c=dtMVstQdH_zFw1NATP4xYyr_D2JPoIl23A5dejiPgw4&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>CHERRY HILL, N.J., July 30, 2014 /PRNewswire/ -- Subaru of America, Inc. today announced that the Insurance Institute of Highway Safety (IIHS) has awarded the 2014 Subaru BRZ (* models manufactured after December 2013) an IIHS 2014 TOP SAFETY PICK award.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays posts bright first-half profits, despite scandals</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fnews.yahoo.com%2fbarclays-says-first-half-net-profit-soars-1-063204926.html&amp;c=lUo7rr8pijSTlPgK2E9N_5WXjBPhoqyGEMEztOI4iFw&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>London (AFP) - Britain's scandal-hit lender Barclays posted surging first-half net profits on Wednesday, sending its share price soaring, as it pushed ahead with a restructuring that will shrink its investment bank division. Earnings after tax surged 68 ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relief rally? Russia markets shrug off sanctions</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.cnbc.com%2fid%2f101877814&amp;c=hQuGFVHZCH11e3wefK40Co0Vv7kzpMc_3IjQAILxJfs&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Russia's MICEX Index rallied 2 percent in morning trade on Wednesday, despite news of the toughest sanctions against the country since the end of the Cold War. Moscow's smaller RTS Index also rose by 2.5 percent the morning after the sanctions were ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays Swings to Profit but Regulatory Issues Persist</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fonline.wsj.com%2farticles%2fbarclays-swings-to-second-quarter-profit-1406700629&amp;c=tX00gSYG1iFKx0Q80myYf669-jNBHf6-ktRCloUvvfM&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday that New York's banking regulator is pushing to install government monitors inside Barclays as part of its probe into suspected foreign exchange manipulation. The regulatory blow came as the bank said it swung to ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald's Can Be Liable For Issues At Franchise-Owned Restaurants, NLRB Rules</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.huffingtonpost.com%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2fmcdonalds-nlrb-joint-employer-ruling_n_5630902.html&amp;c=r3u7_mefSr4Peracd9QVPmYn6ntNTXdyevbxZt2X8ZE&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) — McDonald's is coming under intensifying pressure for labor practices at its U.S. restaurants. The National Labor Relations Board said Tuesday that the world's biggest hamburger chain could be named as a joint employer in several ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. markets: Futures up with Twitter, GDP, Fed in focus</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.marketwatch.com%2fstory%2fus-markets-futures-up-with-twitter-gdp-fed-in-focus-2014-07-30&amp;c=Opgd-86LNgzlKoX6RQuo9rZQ29gudk3cH9xILttOKfU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>MADRID (MarketWatch) — Stock futures moved higher on Wednesday ahead of data expected to show growth in the U.S. economy, and the outcome of the Federal Reserve’s meeting. Tech stocks were already shining as shares of Twitter Inc. (NYSE:TWTR) surged in ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Talks Falter, Bond Default by Argentina Appears Likely</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fdealbook.nytimes.com%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2fas-talks-falter-bond-default-by-argentina-appears-likely%2f&amp;c=LU9eTeqfGVSqQuDfsWvYACsP3DF6zFQHnchY7QpeOow&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Barring a last-minute deal, Argentina will default on billions of dollars of bonds on Wednesday. It would be Argentina’s second default in 13 years. But unlike the last time, when scores of unhappy Argentines took to the street as unemployment rose to 25 ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat scandal takes a bite out of McDonald's sales in Japan</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=15fd9a0e25164ad89b6b5725a52c35d6&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fmoney.cnn.com%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fnews%2fmcdonalds-japan-meat-scandal%2findex.html&amp;c=oDLthnLPog_66J7Zq-2jzKlFwGl3BVSuzlHyaS7xmio&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>A tainted meat scandal that originated in China is now starting to stink up McDonald's sales. The fast food chain's Japanese unit said Tuesday that it will fall short of profit and sales targets for the year, after a longtime meat supplier was shut down ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 03:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>