<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Top Stories - Bing News</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/news/search?q=&amp;p1=%5bNewsVertical+Category%3d%22rt_Politics%22%5d&amp;FORM=NWBTCB&amp;format=RSS</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <copyright>Copyright \xc2\xa9 2014 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <pubDate>7/30/2014 5:44:46 PM</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers complain Obama too aloof with Congress</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fm.philstar.com%2fbreakingnews%2fshow%2f143cb59268e244cac521dfee8c37e85c&amp;c=ql-VaFRRI9_h-YzOzmdXq9YOOiMDSBw77i7u7eyNR54&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"breaking news | Philstar Mobile","summary":["Top GOP leaders got no notice of the $3.7 billion emergency request.","The administration sent contradictory messages about what it wanted to deal with the border crisis.","House and Senate lawmakers in both parties plus several senior congressional aides said this past week that the handling of the proposal by Obama and the White House is emblematic of the administration's rocky relationship with Congress: an ad hoc approach that shuns appeals to opponents and doesn't reward allies."],"source":"m.philstar.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 17:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM wants 'fair immigration system' (From Bicester Advertiser)</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11371594.PM_wants__fair_immigration_system_%2f&amp;c=kU49zJL44tAWarjYGY0AWNqeyGI8bWcw2ScH8SXBWNE&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"PM wants 'fair immigration system' (From Bicester Advertiser)","summary":["The plans will build on reforms announced in January which mean that European migrants must wait three months after arriving in Britain before claiming out-of-work benefits.","Mr Cameron also announced tougher rules to be imposed on universities and colleges which sponsor international students to study in the UK.","A new power to revoke driving licences of illegal immigrants has been used 3,150 since its introduction earlier this month, he said."],"source":"bicesteradvertiser.net"}</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 09:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US senator to propose strong curbs on NSA phone data collection</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.straitstimes.com%2fnews%2fworld%2funited-states%2fstory%2fus-senator-propose-strong-curbs-nsa-phone-data-collection-20140729&amp;c=pryRKO-8GFGlFJoZChTGsdR6_2Q8x-evSg0b6LVhaJ8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"US senator to propose strong curbs on NSA phone data collection","source":"straitstimes.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 16:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh legal challenge as boat people come ashore</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.stockjournal.com.au%2fnews%2fmetro%2fnational%2fgeneral%2ffresh-legal-challenge-as-boat-people-come-ashore%2f2706664.aspx&amp;c=zkygL-wODL7GlKN325GwrWnPcgZ1I70dPLlUgiRBlII&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Fresh legal challenge as boat people come ashore - Metro - National - General","summary":[" Lawyers representing more than 150 Tamil asylum seekers say they will use a High Court hearing to try to quash any attempts to return them to India.","The arrival is a political blow for the Abbott government, which has promoted its success in preventing asylum seeker boats from reaching the Australian mainland.","Prime Minister Tony Abbott said on Saturday the government remains committed to doing whatever it ''morally and ethically can'' to stop the boats."],"source":"stockjournal.com.au"}</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 13:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Strip Club Endorses Democratic Candidate For Congress</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2flasvegas.cbslocal.com%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2farizona-strip-club-endorses-democratic-candidate-for-congress%2f&amp;c=l_FCtg1ghcrOyJtaRv_Q65LJHO79ucLjkEejlzAV3ss&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Arizona Strip Club Endorses Democratic Candidate For Congress \u00ab CBS Las Vegas","summary":["My goal is to help young ladies get their clothes back on.\u00e2\u0080\u009d  Maupin is running in a close race for the 7th District seat against three other Democrats to replace retiring longtime Rep. Ed Pastor."],"source":"lasvegas.cbslocal.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquino impeachment may delay FOI passage, solon warns</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fm.philstar.com%2fbreakingnews%2fshow%2f152b9db318ea24e6ee47518ad21eaac9&amp;c=NtsTOmFdHH2L5BFkcJVXLkOzHSSeIjcE6eaXjEvL40o&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>MANILA, Philippines — The impeachment complaints against President Aquino filed at the House of Representatives may affect the swift passage of the Freedom of Information (FOI) bill, a lawmaker said Wednesday. Deputy Speaker Giorgidi Aggabao believes that there is a big chance that the FOI bill ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 20:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parties bicker over tax plan claims</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11374015.Parties_bicker_over_tax_plan_claims%2f&amp;c=F7NcFsUoVtqpsW2iZvUnlkECq5RrcHbiCLZ1WHZc5Es&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Conservatives and Labour have been forced to fend off rival claims about their future tax plans. The Tories strongly denied that they were planning to move to a "flat tax" system - where everyone pays the same rate of tax regardless of income - after the party's policy chief Oliver Letwin was ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour's so dysfunctional - McBride</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11371600.Labour_s_so_dysfunctional___McBride%2f&amp;c=hBc3Vp0p-udV-Nifj0ccf84i7reviWM_hCwhsGQTbFo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Labour Party is being run in a "totally dysfunctional" way with policies that amount to "a great steaming pile of fudge", according to a former party spin doctor. In an apparent attack on Ed Miliband's leadership, Damian McBride warned that the party has a problem in communicating positive ... </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 16:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers scrutinize costs of beefed up border</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.news4sanantonio.com%2ftemplate%2finews_wire%2fwires.regional.tx%2f32f8d9a4-www.news4sanantonio.com.shtml&amp;c=xRLSUxn2F8eAg3cQKnsL6oRiID-xjS9gKkIyINjeTl0&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) -- A legislative committee is scrutinizing the more-than-$5 million a week Texas spends on beefed-up security along the Mexican border amid a surge of unaccompanied immigrant children. The special Texas House committee on border operations meets Tuesday after the state announced ... </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over Gatwick baggage delays</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11368831.Anger_over_Gatwick_baggage_delays%2f&amp;c=Zrlfd1oDiabVNfPwY-0jJHeAVNoNhlI1cL2EuQhUfB8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Passengers of four airlines at Gatwick airport have been advised to go home without their luggage, after baggage delays for up to five hours this morning. Officials at the airport informed passengers of British Airways flights who had waited more than an hour on their bags being returned, and those ... </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 22:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young adults 'living with parents' (From Bicester Advertiser)</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11371601.Young_adults__living_with_parents_%2f&amp;c=tFJBQsyrF49fVI_aNmH8GpSsUJtitwzadtVFljEFEyw&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Nearly two million working young adults aged between 20 and 34 years old in England are still living with their parents according to Shelter, which is urging stronger action to help the "clipped wing generation" fly the nest. The charity said data it has taken from the Census shows that there are 1 ... </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 22:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bragg pulls strings to end jail ban</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11374023.Bragg_pulls_strings_to_end_jail_ban%2f&amp;c=tuJ4cA2dMcbqZvZBDbx0RJCXAL7spYdRUvJv62Ks8rI&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Protest singer Billy Bragg has helped reverse a government ban on steel-strung guitars in prison. The activist joined politicians and fellow musicians, including former Smiths guitarist Johnny Marr, calling for inmates to be granted use of guitars with steel strings as well as nylon - the latter ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Ruffley to stand down in 2015</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11371489.MP_Ruffley_to_stand_down_in_2015%2f&amp;c=Rkl-pAO8bFPxFO5zot4QoTnZwoPNzQLROIA6cdS2qZE&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>A Tory MP who apologised after receiving a police caution for domestic assault involving his former partner will stand down at the 2015 general election. David Ruffley confirmed in a letter to his local Conservative Association that he will not stand for re-election next year, saying the "protracted ... </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 12:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent pesticide studies urged</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11369404.Transparent_pesticide_studies_urged%2f&amp;c=VJDU-97PrpynAFsaEI8xve26gyHGbgEEtyXKIW_u2c8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>MPs have raised concerns over Government plans to allow pesticide manufacturers to fund "critical" research examining the impact of their chemicals on bees. As part of the Government's draft "national pollinator strategy", which aims to protect bees and other pollinating insects, research into the ... </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 17:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bachmann heads to Mexico border for look at crisis</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.news4sanantonio.com%2ftemplate%2finews_wire%2fwires.regional.tx%2f35f899a0-www.news4sanantonio.com.shtml&amp;c=Vso3M7Xi6eQJ8TKL7jpotOymkiOuR6T9eI-f5HTKuZU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) -- Minnesota Republican Michele Bachmann is spending the weekend along the U.S.-Mexico border to get a firsthand look at an immigration crisis involving Central American youth. Bachmann and Iowa Republican Rep. Steve King were scheduled to arrive in southern Texas on Friday ... </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record on wages 'dismal failure'</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11374014.Record_on_wages__dismal_failure_%2f&amp;c=y2Ut-9vF_pHP-ySJi5FxNpzsA5NfsKMBwWvnvDzLIkc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Working people have suffered the biggest real-terms fall in wages for more than a century under the coalition, Labour is claiming. Shadow chancellor Ed Balls is today publishing figures which, the party says, will show that by the time of the general election next year average earnings after ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right to be forgotten 'unworkable'</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bicesteradvertiser.net%2fnews%2fnational%2fnews%2f11374022.Right_to_be_forgotten__unworkable_%2f&amp;c=lqSRbKdbE5ycLLm6HIlD-8iQMK2noDac0Yg9AZTiYmg&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The European Court of Justice's demand for internet search engines to respect individuals' "right to be forgotten" is unworkable and unreasonable and should be written out of future EU law, a House of Lords committee has said. In a new report, the Lords Home Affairs, Health and Education EU Sub ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valenza Named Sheriff</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=a1c36290d87647e2939344ecfe09ad6d&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.wwntradio.com%2fnews%2fnews.php%2fdisplayType%2farticle%2f16673%2f2014%2f07%2fvalenza-named-sheriff&amp;c=2cFrZ8ttZqPJfd53rt0dGVBX0r8WHqB5zOMsWOvE7mI&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Just before noon on Tuesday July 29th, Governor Robert Bentley made it official by appointing Chief Deputy Donald as interim sheriff effective the day after Sheriff Hughes' resignation becomes effective. Valenza will serve out the remainder of Hughes' term and then, if he wins the general election ... </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>