<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports - Bing News</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/news/search?q=&amp;p1=%5bNewsVertical+Category%3d%22rt_Sports%22%5d&amp;FORM=NWBTCB&amp;format=RSS</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <copyright>Copyright \xc2\xa9 2014 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <pubDate>7/30/2014 5:45:06 PM</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pace, power, touch, technique - meet new Liverpool signing Divock Origi</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.goal.com%2fen-gh%2fnews%2f4363%2fpremier-league%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2f4992486%2fpace-power-touch-technique-meet-new-liverpool-signing-divock&amp;c=3FyRoU_r4GUSKVj6ahA52VE8SJamsMF6dRcoVhiUuMg&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Pace, power, touch, technique - meet new Liverpool signing Divock Origi","summary":["Open-mouthed, he spoke softly and admiringly about the big striker dismantling the opposition defence on his own.","\u201cPace, power, touch, technique \u2013 he\u2019s got the lot,\u201d he cooed.","The youngster he was talking about was Divock Origi."],"source":"goal.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Forshaw: Brentford boss Warburton dismisses transfer talk</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.co.uk%2fsport%2f0%2ffootball%2f28565172&amp;c=Cu0-2uxcKV9rVZPlAr_Fnu4wJNv8PA94XlohSbg8YiY&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"BBC Sport - Adam Forshaw: Brentford boss Warburton dismisses transfer talk","summary":[" Brentford manager Mark Warburton has insisted they have no intention of selling midfielder Adam Forshaw."],"source":"bbc.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Cherington considering multiple trades</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bostonglobe.com%2fsports%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2fred-sox-notes-ben-cherington-burning-phone-lines%2fDWlK8V6Ux2sLh7OoVMVYaJ%2fstory.html&amp;c=pNOFnWFU6xih339iqLCoMXzPYQWfDOPwpjPJX_Z8VP8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Red Sox notes: GM Ben Cherington burning up the phone lines - Sports","summary":[" The Red Sox are a last-place team and general manager Ben Cherington is wearing down his cell phone battery collecting trade proposals.","Continue reading below  \u201cWe\u2019ve got a number of guys that are of interest to a number of teams.","The Red Sox appeared listless in a 14-1 loss to Toronto on Monday."],"source":"bostonglobe.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesut Ozil, Diego Costa and Wilfried Zaha... the Premier League player at your club with a point to prove this season</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2fsport%2ffootball%2farticle-2710510%2fMesut-Ozil-Diego-Costa-Wilfried-Zaha-Premier-League-player-club-point-prove-season.html&amp;c=LkQkS-8TvWlH1DzJQeG5AWYzZb3zKjeIIaW0qdaYGtk&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Mesut Ozil, Diego Costa and Wilfried Zaha... the Premier League player at your club with a point to prove this season","summary":["Some will need to rebuild reputations after a bad season or must justify a massive transfer fee; others have been handed opportunities via squad reshuffles and promotions to show that they are good enough to step up.\u00a0  Whatever the reason, they all face huge pressure to deliver in the forthcoming season.","It would be great to see some of those old flourishes, if injuries and recent experiences haven\u2019t left too much of a scar.\u00a0  Last chance?","He was voted the best player in the second tier last season and now has to show that he, and indeed his team, can cut it in the Premier League."],"source":"dailymail.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vidal right to consider Juventus future but joining Manchester United would be a huge mistake</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.goal.com%2fen-ke%2fnews%2f4744%2feditorials%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2f4991326%2fvidal-crazy-to-join-man-utd&amp;c=7HtAh1isUlC_32FiBJ3EBbw5TxPYhB5J8E5wkjnpH4E&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Vidal right to consider Juventus future but joining Manchester United would be a huge mistake","summary":["It's quite clear for me that I'm the best in my role.\u201d  Even if he says so himself, few will argue that there is a better central midfielder on the planet than Arturo Vidal.","Indeed, in the 2014 Goal 50, the partly-converted Philipp Lahm was the only player in the Chilean's role to finish above him.","In terms of completeness \u2013 no one even gets close to Vidal."],"source":"goal.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals, CB Patrick Peterson: $70M</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fespn.go.com%2fnew-york%2fnfl%2fstory%2f_%2fid%2f11284202%2farizona-cardinals-sign-patrick-peterson-five-year-contract-extension&amp;c=cfOrgJ0fLlVz8OsbrMcfttHm04mMHHC4F9UPzBnqLy0&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The Arizona Cardinals have agreed with Patrick Peterson on a five-year contract extension, a deal the Pro Bowler said Tuesday night is worth $70 million with $48 million guaranteed, which makes him the highest-paid cornerback in the NFL. Peterson's ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being told I was too small by Celtic motivated me - Andy Robertson</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.co.uk%2fsport%2f0%2ffootball%2f28559164&amp;c=39u8_lSN7JnBEs3JK2weKeBJ9OkuIvwdq9hBypFO5kU&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Hull City new-boy Andrew Robertson says being let go by Celtic for "being too small" has made him even more determined to succeed at the top level. The 20-year-old, who joined the Tigers from Dundee United for £2.85m, says his height was behind Celtic's ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea refuse to print names of Romelu Lukaku and Thibaut Courtois on shirts after failing to hand pair squad numbers</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2fsport%2ffootball%2farticle-2710626%2fChelsea-refuse-print-names-Romelu-Lukaku-Thibaut-Courtois-shirts-failing-hand-pair-squad-numbers.html&amp;c=I0ze5bk233SmPhP-WrOiYpNmZIZR94F5wgMbOT56Dpk&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Chelsea fans wanting Romelu Lukaku or Thibaut Courtois on their new shirts will be left disappointed - as the club shop will not print their names. The Belgian duo have yet to meet up with Jose Mourinho’s side for pre-season, and have such not been ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zaha, Kagawa make case to United in Inter win</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.supersport.com%2ffootball%2fpre-season-tour%2fnews%2f140730%2fZaha_Kagawa_make_case_to_United_in_Inter_win&amp;c=HNr7iZimgDI-gD0RCy-zlaoEeFTQn_URJuGTW28m3dw&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Manchester United remained undefeated under new Dutch manager Louis van Gaal after defeating Inter Milan 5-3 on penalty kicks on Tuesday following a goalless draw. Scouting attacking talent for an English Premier League season only 18 days away, Van Gaal ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy, confident Phillip Thomas catching coaches’ eyes</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.washingtonpost.com%2fblogs%2ffootball-insider%2fwp%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fhealthy-confident-phillip-thomas-catching-coaches-eyes%2f&amp;c=NFM3KRcnvSLjjBNfX21gQw_oG2K7qaQERVYkh6vJu44&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>RICHMOND – As he has watched Phillip Thomas through five training camp practices, a couple of things in particular have stood out to defensive backs coach Raheem Morris. For one, Thomas has fully regained the athleticism and quickness that made him an ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic effort needed from Waratahs against Crusaders in Super Rugby final</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.smh.com.au%2frugby-union%2funion-news%2folympic-effort-needed-from-waratahs-against-crusaders-in-super-rugby-final-20140730-zyjvp.html&amp;c=4pp5i-dKAGERBXcEUnj9AfV_FIbO6t5QGkD1Plpyoj8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Be wewy wewy quiet. I'm hunting wabbits. Well, at the very least, hunting Crusaders here in Christchurch, the home city of the champion team just about to leave for our own Sydney Town for the final of the Super Rugby on Saturday night at the Olympic Stadium.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning Roar: The Lions take two fields</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fespn.go.com%2fblog%2fdetroit-lions%2fpost%2f_%2fid%2f9422%2fmorning-roar-the-lions-take-two-fields&amp;c=Ul8bAUP4pnjjongfiQ-C8Q4ZZeTLQqUfkSCxsXb2w_0&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>To do that, the Lions are employing two fields during training camp, but Caldwell insisted not to read too much into who is participating on what field even though the majority of presumed starters all end up on the same field together. "We try to make ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In debate over MASN rights, MLB rules for Washington Nationals, but fight continues</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.washingtonpost.com%2fsports%2fnationals%2fin-debate-over-masn-rights-mlb-rules-for-washington-nationals-but-fight-continues%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2f65a3af4e-1774-11e4-9e3b-7f2f110c6265_story.html&amp;c=ad2VlTu7FJgByWEKhYsrRIhh6mbNgESv9vOnqGt7zRM&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Major League Baseball’s arbitration panel ruled in favor of the Washington Nationals in their longstanding, contentious dispute with the Baltimore Orioles over television rights fees from the Mid-Atlantic Sports Network, a person familiar with the ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer news: Birmingham City sign Denny Johnstone from Celtic</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww1.skysports.com%2ffootball%2fnews%2f11694%2f9400147%2ftransfer-news-birmingham-city-sign-denny-johnstone-from-celtic&amp;c=KpsHlvL5dI8qFL9oDNIikwRHhJwsfbSeJNoycI2R928&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Birmingham City have signed teenage forward Denny Johnstone from Celtic on a three-year contract. The 19-year-old Scotland U19 international has opted to join the Blues after rejecting a new deal from the Hoops. Birmingham have agreed compensation for ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Blackadder takes shot at Waratahs money men</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.smh.com.au%2frugby-union%2funion-news%2ftodd-blackadder-takes-shot-at-waratahs-money-men-20140730-zyjbr.html&amp;c=auS220R956knoFBm_1ouQ9h9TN7pSB5hrX3S9M2FsAc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Todd Blackadder cannot believe the Waratahs have ditched their fortress to chase the almighty dollar. If Crusaders coach Blackadder was in counterpart Michael Cheika’s shoes he would never allow anyone, or any amount of cash, to persuade him to give up ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England v India, Third Test, Day 4 Live: Cook, Ballance take the lead past 300</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.firstpost.com%2fsports%2fengland-v-india-third-test-day-4-live-dhoni-fights-to-save-follow-on-1639899.html&amp;c=8pkbBiLw-UtO5NdQ8Vca9QLd3ScljBzbYDRgqolQurc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Click here if you are accessing this page on your mobile phone. Day 3 report: James Anderson and Stuart Broad each took three wickets to leave India in trouble on 323 for eight, 246 runs adrift of England, after the third day of the third test on Tuesday.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United need time to learn my methods</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.iol.co.za%2fcapetimes%2funited-need-time-to-learn-my-methods-1.1727938&amp;c=GcaBrb8SmI-rVjuh1au14dqxpJCGt4nzB4VTm88fMNY&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>New Manchester United manager Louis van Gaal has warned fans not to expect instant success, saying it will take three months for his players to get used to his style and methods. The Dutchman, brought in following the sacking of David Moyes less than 10 ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN suspends Smith for comments on abuse</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ffinance.yahoo.com%2fnews%2fespn-suspends-smith-comments-abuse-112653971.html&amp;c=szk6sBaeIvPTDp9erEceFsCoHUvvS0K0zdoVvLwfh1k&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) -- ESPN has suspended outspoken sportscaster Stephen A. Smith for a week because of his comments about domestic abuse suggesting women should make sure that they don't do anything to provoke an attack. Smith's commentary occurred during a ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer news: Harry Redknapp confirms QPR interest in Norwich midfielder Leroy Fer</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww1.skysports.com%2ffootball%2fnews%2f11661%2f9400130%2ftransfer-news-harry-redknapp-confirms-qpr-interest-in-norwich-midfielder-leroy-fer&amp;c=WScJno24YGpOp572nfqbGJrnKVbRFbshIC03DpE3-t8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>QPR manager Harry Redknapp has confirmed Norwich midfielder Leroy Fer is one of a number of players he is hoping to add to his squad before the start of the Premier League season. The Dutchman was part of Louis van Gaal’s Netherlands squad for the World ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Reus transfer latest: Manchester United, Liverpool and Bayern Munich line-up to sign Germany international</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=ff13d48c5a59449f9916b74d6b6a10e3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.independent.co.uk%2fsport%2ffootball%2ftransfers%2fmarco-reus-transfer-latest-manchester-united-liverpool-and-bayern-munich-lineup-to-sign-germany-international-9637480.html&amp;c=k0GoDmGEJLHFwUYDvFud-sLSY2EuvokxcWAYeNZxUN8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>A host of European giants are reportedly queuing up to sign Marco Reus amid reports that the Germany international has rejected a new contract at Borussia Dortmund. The attacking midfielder's current contract runs until 2017 but with the club eager to ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>