<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sci/Tech - Bing News</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/news/search?q=&amp;p1=%5bNewsVertical+Category%3d%22rt_ScienceAndTechnology%22%5d&amp;FORM=NWBTCB&amp;format=RSS</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <copyright>Copyright \xc2\xa9 2014 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <pubDate>7/30/2014 5:45:15 PM</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>OKCupid row: Hurrah for our less than perfect matches! Online dating isn't a science</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.telegraph.co.uk%2fwomen%2fsex%2f11000204%2fOKCupid-online-dating-row-Hurrah-for-our-less-than-perfect-matches.html&amp;c=wsR5aGpxkXwcF84C_MwqJIH6tt7MEIIj0l22u8xfrHw&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"OKCupid online dating row: Hurrah for our less than perfect matches!","summary":[" Yes, the all-important 'match' rating - a figure that is supposed to tell   users how well they will connect with other daters - became an invention.","Rudder added, \u201cMaybe people just like each other because they think they\u2019re   supposed to?","It can\u2019t be predicted by simple maths."],"source":"telegraph.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH: 'Electrical storm' of thoughts deep within a zebrafish's brain as 80,000 neurons fire off</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2fsciencetech%2farticle-2710612%2fWATCH-Electrical-storm-thoughts-deep-zebrafishs-brain-80-000-neurons-fire-off.html&amp;c=O5fQ9nFtD3OQhMG7H_5YW2_R3V71DN5yZ0UUcFeekPI&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"WATCH: 'Electrical storm' of thoughts deep within a zebrafish's brain as 80,000 neurons fire off","summary":["A new technique, called light-sheet imaging, was able to capture 80 per cent of the fish\u2019s neurons in action, showing the electrical storm within its brain in unprecedented detail.","The study could allow researchers to better understand the \u2018rules\u2019 of the brain activity by mapping exactly which neurons are responsible for certain movements.","Scroll down for video\u00a0  In this image neurons in a zebrafish brain are coloured by the direction of motion they are associated."],"source":"dailymail.co.uk"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People say techies are invading San Francisco. They said the same about my immigrant grandfather</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.washingtonpost.com%2fposteverything%2fwp%2f2014%2f07%2f30%2fi-grew-up-in-san-francisco-now-im-one-of-the-techies-displacing-local-residents%2f&amp;c=yhxOfScbrav4LDEyZuCI2LF7ESwxs0p-6mMirEawUT4&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"People say techies are invading San Francisco. They said the same about my immigrant grandfather","summary":[" I\u00e2\u0080\u0099ve begun to worry that San Francisco is slipping back into the past.","If you\u00e2\u0080\u0099re not from here, you might not notice it amid the sparkle of new office towers, the pageant of initial public offerings and the people wearing glasses that can also make phone calls and tell you the euro-dollar exchange rate.","Growing up in San Francisco as a third-generation Chinese American, I remember learning about the city\u00e2\u0080\u0099s uneasy relationship with new arrivals."],"source":"washingtonpost.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hummingbirds edge out helicopters in hover contest</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bbc.com%2fnews%2f28563737&amp;c=3cRjgJCvJLBF1ogv8zTDnNxL25_L6uolOmnhDsXLRYY&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"BBC News - Hummingbirds edge out helicopters in hover contest","summary":["This is according to a study comparing hummingbirds with one of the world's most advanced micro-helicopters.","Researchers found that - in terms of the power they require to lift their weight - the best hummingbird was over 20% more efficient than the helicopter.","Lead researcher Prof David Lentink, from Stanford University in California, explained that the flight performance of a hummingbird - the only bird capable of sustained hovering - was extremely difficult to measure."],"source":"bbc.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 03:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysts rush to lift Twitter price targets on results blowout</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.marketwatch.com%2fstory%2fanalysts-rush-to-lift-twitter-price-targets-on-results-blowout-2014-07-30&amp;c=yV_-tDIZSdg-1zNLPcNClRSCEOPOdwZMa5M0cIA6Ls8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>{"title":"Analysts rush to lift Twitter price targets on results blowout - Market Extra","summary":["Late Tuesday, the shares jumped more than 30% after the company\u00e2\u0080\u0099s adjusted profit and revenue surpassed expectations, and its outlook on full-year revenue was also better than a previous estimate.","Analysts had also been holding their breath over the tally for monthly active users.","Twitter edged past expectations for 267 million monthly active users with a count of 271 million."],"source":"marketwatch.com"}</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vince Cable says UK will have 'fleets' of driverless cars as he admits he doesn't even own a Sat Nav</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.telegraph.co.uk%2ftechnology%2f11000166%2fVince-Cable-says-UK-will-have-fleets-of-driverless-cars-as-he-admits-he-doesnt-even-own-a-Sat-Nav.html&amp;c=577Cue5qzP8NomVUeONLdlrv7_caX3cvNOpa9OJW0Q8&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>New driverless technology will see "fleets" of satellite controlled vehicles on Britain's roads within years, Vince Cable has claimed as he admits he doesn't even have a basic SatNav device installed in his own car. The Business Secretary has announced ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter zooms 25% on strong sales and mobile growth</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fmoney.cnn.com%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2ftechnology%2fsocial%2ftwitter-earnings%2findex.html&amp;c=28eodF9W0gOvrYGwtn3pxjQ5-rAkm-xxqEn4sBOt0I4&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Things are looking up for Twitter -- or at least, for its stock price. Twitter (TWTR, Tech30) shares surged 25% in premarket trading Wednesday after it posted strong second-quarter sales. Twitter's better-than-expected quarterly report helped allay fears ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 03:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Swings to Profit as Expenses Decline</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fonline.wsj.com%2farticles%2fsprint-swings-to-profit-1406720666&amp;c=1FX1Bm-yabiX83OFWeUkQqVu1nykx9HXZ2ULT08VQ84&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Sprint Corp. S +4.71% Sprint Corp. U.S.: NYSE $ 8.00 +0.36 +4.71% July 29, 2014 4:02 pm Volume (Delayed 15m) : 27.40M AFTER HOURS $ 8.04 +0.04 +0.50% July 29, 2014 7:59 pm Volume (Delayed 15m) : 1.64M P/E Ratio N/A Market Cap $30.14 Billion Dividend Yield ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now that's a toothy grin! Fearless photographer gets dangerously close to great white sharks at feeding time - WITHOUT a safety cage</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.dailymail.co.uk%2ftravel%2farticle-2710495%2fSpectacular-shark-photos-Cameraman-snaps-incredible-images-great-whites.html&amp;c=begHZsJlnOOSIozHA188PNOZUPpI5yml08cfbaWXcAQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>For most people, sharks are magnificent creatures – but definitely the sort of beasts you would want to avoid coming into close contact with in a dark corner of the sea. In fact, given the chance to get up close and personal with the most menacing of all ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flipkart's Bansals nearly as rich as Infosys co-founders</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ftimesofindia.indiatimes.com%2ftech%2ftech-news%2fFlipkarts-Bansals-nearly-as-rich-as-Infosys-co-founders%2farticleshow%2f39265726.cms&amp;c=3Chvmy6uby7VqOEH-VN4JFaXMiGV22_Rz7BEl3TLy0g&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>BANGALORE: The Bansals of Flipkart — Sachin and Binny — now boast of a combined net worth in excess of $1 billion, inching closer to that of Bangalore's iconic tech billionaires N R Narayana Murthy and Nandan Nilekani of Infosys. The fresh $1-billion ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Mario’s New Benz Can’t Spark Sales of Wii U Console</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bloomberg.com%2fnews%2f2014-07-30%2fsuccess-of-new-mario-game-fails-to-revitalize-nintendo.html&amp;c=6Dh3alIC3XfK9bJ6j6kvf1ahgcbi0Zk8VNe8XN__uWc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Super Mario upgraded to a Mercedes-Benz in the newest version of his racing game, yet that wasn’t enough to keep Nintendo Co. (7974)’s Wii U from looking like a lemon. Mario Kart 8 and a lineup of figurines that interact with games are part of the ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaulterus launches BitCan™ - Next Generation Cloud Backup and Recovery Service for Databases and Files</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ffinance.yahoo.com%2fnews%2fvaulterus-launches-bitcan-next-generation-120300526.html&amp;c=Sh7SIEpGPKtnUPGuqhi60F7Jxlglx6WkMSm33TEcWhs&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>SAN MATEO, Calif., July 30, 2014 /PRNewswire/ -- Vaulterus, LLC, a leading cloud based backup as a service company, announced the launch of its next generation database and file backup and recovery solution - BitCan™. BitCan™ enables seamless ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warding Off Lions With Mobiles Shows African Technology Boom</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.bloomberg.com%2fnews%2f2014-07-29%2fwarding-off-lions-with-cell-phones-shows-african-technology-boom.html&amp;c=cO5aYjKhyPENo2o_7AsATupYlp62eHFxwHBymrbagSc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>If Emily Parsitau wanted to light her home to ward off lions and intruders, she had to walk for an hour to buy kerosene at the nearest store. Now, she uses a SIM card. The farmer’s four-roomed home in Kisamis, a rural area on the fringe of Kenya’s Rift ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPhone-Ready Apps Mean Teens Tracked Without Calling Home</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.businessweek.com%2fnews%2f2014-07-30%2fiphone-ready-apps-mean-teens-tracked-without-calling-home&amp;c=2mqplFQRFVzGDqtdiMThpCIoe0QiFz3QCfMv8C0b040&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Becca Ludlum knows better than to expect her teen son, Michael, to call home as he skateboards from the mall to the park to friends’ homes on long summer days. Ludlum instead relies on a downloadable smartphone application called Life360 that uses ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say goodbye to Facebook Gifts</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fnews.yahoo.com%2fgoodbye-facebook-gifts-115211865.html&amp;c=OCGkUIuwpl2xGhzMkSp1tLuBVn2tDCpKo-PI2a7uZDc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>The social network has decided that its Gifts feature is not working and that from now on it will instead focus on helping others promote their own gifts and goods via the site. When Facebook Gifts went live in the US in September 2012, it actually sold ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 05:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India set to become Amazon's fastest-growing market: CEO Jeff Bezos</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2ftimesofindia.indiatimes.com%2ftech%2ftech-news%2fIndia-set-to-become-Amazons-fastest-growing-market-CEO-Jeff-Bezos%2farticleshow%2f39298577.cms&amp;c=W0VWS_8wkbYT_nKi_pzlFyfN8MNW_HKAzA4LDaZZIwo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>MUMBAI: Amazon.com on Wednesday said it will invest a further $2 billion in India just a day after the country's largest e-tailer Flipkart attracted $1 billion of fresh funds, raising the stakes in a nascent but fast-growing e-commerce sector. Amazon ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Colonize an Alien Planet? Send 40,000 People</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fnews.yahoo.com%2fwant-colonize-alien-planet-send-40-000-people-113509947.html&amp;c=21HmHiCdw9-31qvRweI5j64uwEGVPtobLqeCrdXBBHc&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>This story was updated at 1:00 p.m. EDT on July 28. If humanity ever wants to colonize a planet beyond the solar system, it's going to need a really big spaceship. The founding population of an interstellar colony should consist of 20,000 to 40,000 people ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft facing anti-monopoly investigation in China</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.theguardian.com%2ftechnology%2f2014%2fjul%2f30%2fmicrosoft-facing-anti-monopoly-investigation-in-china&amp;c=s_bjYsnzmN2l_2CqP0PeN8gZREIgbhTi8A5MxwSaX9w&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>Yusuf Mehdi speaks during the presentation of the Xbox One in Shanghai. A Chinese investigation into Microsoft is probably targeting its ‘monopoly’ of the country’s operation system market. Photograph: Johannes Eisele/AFP/Getty Images Microsoft said ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Reveals Its Master Plan For Growing As Big As Facebook</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fwww.forbes.com%2fsites%2fjeffbercovici%2f2014%2f07%2f29%2ftwitter-reveals-its-master-plan-for-growing-as-big-as-facebook%2f&amp;c=q2msRt79YuiAIDjcJd5zDhuhsPK3DcPyeHYTy5qpSmo&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>“The largest information network in the world”: Prepare to hear that phrase out of the mouth of Twitter Twitter CEO Dick Costolo a lot in the coming months. Costolo and his fellow executives used it four or five times on Tuesday’s second-quarter ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon to Invest $2 Billion in India</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com/news/apiclick.aspx?ref=FexRss&amp;aid=&amp;tid=b3c407b8641445688751c3fcb56909d3&amp;url=http%3a%2f%2fonline.wsj.com%2farticles%2famazon-to-invest-2-billion-in-india-1406700828&amp;c=HxGSOYaJq_U_9o_9EDi130h_4DX2QMFRR7mkIbXm3DQ&amp;mkt=en-sg</link>
      <description>BANGALORE, India— Amazon.com Inc. AMZN -0.13% Amazon.com Inc. U.S.: Nasdaq $ 320.00 -0.41-0.13% July 29, 2014 4:00 pm Volume (Delayed 15m) : 2.84M AFTER HOURS $ 320.57 +0.57 +0.18% July 29, 2014 7:59 pm Volume (Delayed 15m) : 43,694 P/E Ratio 820.51 ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 04:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>